[Music]
[Música]
Okay, familiar little topic, allows, important,
bueno familiar temita permite importante
powerful termite, I don't know what
termita potente no sé que lo que ha
happened, but Juan is very angry,
pasado pero yo juanes está muy [__]
well, very loaded, we're not going to
bueno muy cargado tampoco nos vamos a
see what happened because
ver qué es lo que ha pasado porque al
apparently they had an
parecer han tenido un comentario
unfortunate comment with more if it is not summoned,
desafortunado con más si no se convoca
in addition, if I more have a girl person, a
además si a mí más tiene persona chica
good part of pretty, nice, it
buena parte de guapa simpática
seems to me that she is a girl who is going to
me parece que es una chica que va a
sweep the internet world as a
arrasar en el mundo de internet como
presenter, whatever you do, a girl
presentadora haga lo que hagas una chica
who transmits very good vibes, okay,
que transmite muy buen rollo vale
let's see what happened, what
vamos a ver qué es lo que ha pasado cuál
was the comment that you didn't like
ha sido el comentario que no le ha
there, Juan said that they have made it
gustado ahí dio juan que la han hecho
more and okay, I have changed the background here, I don't
más y vale he cambiado aquí el fondo no
know if you will like it more or less, I know that I am
sé si os gustará más o menos sé que soy
a restless ass with the overlay, but it is that it does
un culo inquieto con el overlay pero es
not finish, it does not finish
que no me termina no me termina de
convincing me, okay then I will try with
convencer vale entonces voy probando con
chairs and so on, let's see what happens, he said that
sillas y demás vamos a ver qué pasa dijo
they said something like that, I say something
que han dicho algo así es que digo algo
about a dessert, well, it's something like but I with
de un postre pues es algo de pero yo con
more if I eat the dessert or something like that, it was
más si me como el postre o algo así fue
something like that, who said something like but we
algo así quién dijo algo de pero lo
were commenting on it here and I just left  to
comentábamos aquí y yo justo me fui a
[ __ ] and they said something about
[__] y dijeron algo de
with you in the chat I was commenting
con vosotros en el chat yo comentaba
here with you we watched it in
aquí con vosotros lo veíamos en el de
ibai's but we were commenting on it here and I
ibai pero lo comentábamos aquí y yo
just went to [ __ ] and they said something about
justo me fui a [__] y dijeron algo de
[Music]
[Música]
like in the disaster chef that I don't know what
así en el disaster chef que no sé cuál
the truth was I think it was the third or the
fue la verdad creo que el tercero o el
second that I didn't know because I
segundo que yo no conocía porque yo ese
clearly watched that program in its entirety and I
programa claro que los vio enteros y lo
watched it with you and I didn't hear it at
vi con vosotros y no lo escuché en
any time I think I was
ningún momento yo creo que yo estaba
just [ __ ] or do you remember that at one
justo [__] o acordáis que en un
point I went to [ __ ] and I was
momento yo me fui a [__] y estuve un
out of the chat for a while because the disaster
rato fuera del chat porque los disaster
che I've been watching it here with
che yo lo he estado viendo aquí con
you in the chat I was commenting that with
vosotros en el chat yo comentaba que con
you we watched it in ibai's but we
vosotros lo veíamos en el de ibai pero
were commenting on it here and I just went to
lo comentábamos aquí y yo justo me fui a
[ __ ] and they said something about
[__] y dijeron algo de
[Music]
[Música]
if they told me it was pino who said something
si me dijeron que fue pino que dijo algo
about
de
[Music]
[Música]
or to say something about a dessert well it's
o que diga algo de un postre pues es
something but I with more if I eat the
algo de pero yo con más si me como el
dessert or something like that maybe he
postre o algo así igual
's a friend of man he
es amigo del hombre
never really convinced me he came
nunca me terminó de convencer vino
to put rebequita around here because I'm
a poner a rebequita por aquí que tengo
cold family
frío familia
plugs in so many things that I never
enchufa tantas cosas que nunca me
remove stadiums it doesn't convince me in the end I'm
quita estadios no me convence al final
going to put it like I had it before and
voy a poner como lo tenía antiguamente y
even Diego Bechis is very serious but they
hasta diego bechis rayando mucho pero lo
see it light there is a
ven light
click you know there is a click
hay clic sabe hay clic
but the click is here
pero está aquí el clic
how ugly
qué feo
what is missing
qué falta
is not the act either I don't know how I would
tampoco es tampoco el acto no sé cómo
present it I think that I would feel
presentaría yo creo que a mí me sentaría
bad about
mal
something if they tell you that you weren't
una cosa que te digan que tú no habías
very pretty of your women very pretty it is
muy guapa de tus mujeres muy guapas son
a compliment okay or that you accidentally
un halago vale o que tú sin querer
heard that someone in private has said she
escuché que alguien en privado ha dicho
is very good they
ya está muy buena
said them in private they haven't said it to your
las dicho en privada no te han dicho en
face and in the end it is a compliment don't
la cara y al final es un halago no se
think that your relative is very good
piensen que tu pariente está muy buena
but since in public something he tells her I would
pero ya que en público cosa le diga yo
eat her dessert with her
con ella me comería el postre
the overdrive looks good let's see you like it
queda bien el overdrive a ver os gusta
the truth we like to give your opinion a chevy give your
la verdad nos gusta opinar un chevy
opinion you leave it and it doesn't convince me anymore
opinad ustedes lo dejas y ya no me
it was something like that they
fue algo así
said first about marriage that was when it was
se dijeron primero lo del matrimonio que
when more and he said no I am
ahí fue cuando más y soltó no yo estoy
already engaged I don't know what to go to why is it
ya prometida no sé qué ir a por qué es
because I didn't know it
porque no sabía
is ugly the truth is that I don't like
está feo la verdad que no me gusta
leaving it looks very cool if this one is good
dejarlo queda muy chulos si está bien
no let's see if  I'll do one thing
este no a ver si hago una cosa
maybe we can save it with this
a lo mejor con esto lo podemos salvar
but I don't know what it really does
pero es que no sé qué hace de verdad
I asked Tina but
le pedí a tina pero
let's leave it like this in black and white
vamos a dejarlo así en blanco y negro
at least it looks better ugly ugly
por lo menos queda mejor
Mondays don't fit in this we like it nobody likes it
feo feo los lunes no pegan en esto nos
no then it doesn't
gusta nos gusta a nadie no entonces no
leave the hair time removed but what do I
deja la hora de pelo quita pero que
put there was a bad one we can not for nothing
pongo había una mala podemos no por nada
also I tell you it
también os digo
doesn't
no me
collect less air and we see it here
recopila menos aire y lo vemos aquí
now finally we
ahora por fin
leave it without a background the letters we
lo dejamos sin fondo las letras
remove the letters these too like
quitamos las letras estas también
that it's fine we
así está bien
remove the background left it in black and
quitamos el fondo lo dejó en blanco y
white the black that the black looks epic
negro el negro que el negro queda épico
the letter is ugly
la letra está fea
and such we remove everything then I remove the
y tal lo quitamos todo entonces quito la
net like that we do
red
n't leave it because so yes I can't
así no dejamos porque así que sí no
put seen here well you don't
puedo poner visto aquí bueno ustedes no
davis one
davis uno
but it's to fill the screen no
pero es por rellenar la pantalla no
also I tell you this is
también te digo
horrible this
esta horrible
horrible it's very loaded
esta horrible es muy cargado
and television also doesn't look
y televisión también no se ve nada
professional at all
profesional
then buy me a zeta
luego me compra un zeta
what is that viso you don't even know what
qué es eso del viso usted ni sabe lo que
mink is virus out
es el visón virus fuera
like that
así
or rather a little bit longer
o sea ya un poquito más largo
already it already a
ya lo
little bit sends it
ya lo poquito manda
bigger to the screen but then I
más grande a la pantalla pero entonces
cover it up  I
la tapo yo un poco
take it off a little and Javi I take it
quitad y javi
off I
me quito yo
make it like this let's
make it así
see family like this like this
a ver familia así
often everything looks bad on me in the
así a menudo todo me queda mal en el
overlay everything looks terrible and
overlay todo me queda fatal
messy let's see let's see family let's see well let's
desordenada a ver a ver familia
see family but t family is waiting for you
a ver familia pero te espera t
like this let's
familia así
see tell me McCann also take off your
a ver dime mccann también quítate la
clothes it's more professional I hear
ropa es más profesional oigo se halla
hunger is found and Lorca next to uncle
hambre y lorca lado tío
go to hell it's like this too not the
ir al [__] ya es así también no el
black one like this if we can leave it
negro así si lo podemos dejarlo
like this if we can't leave come on it's that if I
así si no podemos dejar venga es que si
put it and I put it like the old one that
lo ponía y lo pongo como el antiguo que
put it on full screen and it takes up the
lo ponía a pantalla completa y ocupa
whole screen there were things that I
toda la pantalla había cosas que yo
covered we got away with the camera
tapaba se nos escapaba con la cámara
then we'll see
entonces ya veremos
also tell us
también nos diga
the scientist jumps and sweet really I do
el científico saltos y dulce de verdad
n't know why he asks for an opinion or
que no sé ni para qué pide opinión ni
anyone it's that I do
nadie
n't know why I ask for your opinion
es que no se me para que os pido opinión
and negative you
y negativo
don't support me nobody
no me apoyáis nadie nos
listens to us although we are ready and then
escucha aunque estamos listos y luego
something like a dessert it
algo de un postre
's that I don't know he doesn't
es que no sé no se
put his foot in it because I was going to leave he told me
mete la pata porque me iba a ir me dijo
the comment but I don't know if it was like that exactly you
el comentario pero no sé si fue así tal
know I don't
sabe
know if it was like that exactly Caesar
no sé si fue así tal cual
Caesar
el cesar
and the  inopportune man how inopportune that
y el inoportuno tío que inoportuno que
you are invited to an event and you make those kinds
te inviten a un evento y hagas ese tipo
of comments about the guests well she
de comentarios de las invitadas bueno no
is not even a guest she is the
es ni siquiera una invitada es la
presenter it is that I do not care even
presentadora es que me da igual incluso
if she is
si está
single or not she is single it
soltera o no está soltera
was not when more and she said that she was
fue cuando más y dijo que estaba
engaged but it was not something of the dessert I eat it
prometida pero no fue algo de el postre
something like that
me lo como algo así
mistakenly where is the click
equivocadamente dónde está el clic me
can you send me the clip please
podéis mandar el clip por fa
can you send me the click please she
me podéis mandar el clic por fa
told me this comment and there I I did not
me dijo este comentario y ahí yo yo no
know I heard that and I said listen to me
lo sabía yo escuché eso y dije escúchame
this is already a cola the truth I mean I
esto ya es una colada la verdad o sea
can try that they are older people
puedo intentar de que son personas más
but [ __ ] I mean it does not matter no it
mayores tal pero [__] o sea da igual no
is not an excuse for anything you
no es excusa para nada
know you are on a program and [ __ ]
sabe estás en un programa y [__] te está
a lot of people are watching you there they already said it
viendo mucha gente hay que ya lo dijeron
in the video let's
en el vídeo
see I'm going to look for the sodium
a ver voy a buscar el sodio
surely there are videos on youtube of her
seguro que hay vídeos en youtube de su
life or something
vida o algo
surely of her life
seguro de su vida
what does she do with that thumbnail
qué hace con esa miniatura yo
because it has my live to the thumbnail
porque tiene mi directo a la miniatura
of the chocas
del chocas
I just realized that my live
me acabo de dar cuenta que mi directo
has the thumbnail of the choco song
tiene la miniatura del choco canción
I have put
tengo puesto
to you what thumbnails does the one come out with
a ustedes qué miniaturas sale el one con
the click to be worth in which it says
el click a valer en el cual lo pone
be consistent dude, what you're
ser consecuente tío de lo que estás
saying to whoever you're saying it to,
diciendo a quien se lo está diciendo
you know
sabe
how brothers-in-law
como cuñados
presented the dish, he
presentaron el plato
says something like she puts that
dice algo así como ella te pone ese
plate in front of you and you go straight to dessert,
plato y pasas directamente al postre
completely out of place,
completamente fuera de lugar
completely out of place, I mean, I've been
completamente fuera de lugar o sea llevo
hearing those things and obviously I say
escucho esas cosas y obviamente digo yo
this, which is because of them, because of me, the
esto que es por ellas por mí el
comment was directed at me but
comentario lo dirigió hacia mí pero
obviously in Belgium, what the [ __ ] is
obviamente en bélgica que [__] lo que es
empathy and caring for
la empatía y el de tenerle cariño a
someone, can I make things
alguien puedo hacer que la cosa a ti
hurt you too? You know, grandmother's job, there's
también te duelan sabe la tarea de las
an ingredient,
hay un ingrediente
you put Tomas and for dinner and go
a ti te pones tomás y para cenar y vaya
straight to dessert, under the police,
directo a la postre bajo el poli
I had seen this here, I was
esto yo lo había visto aquí yo estaba
[ __ ]
[__]
this more and for dinner,
esto más y para cenar
unnecessary, there's one more ingredient, you
innecesarias haya un ingrediente
put Tomas and for dinner and dance,
a ti te pones tomás y para cenar y baile
another for dessert, Bauer pole,
otro a la postre bauer pole
this, me, the two grandparents and the two old men
esto yo los dos abuelos y los dos viejos
saying that with a
diciendo eso
face like I was going to go
la cara de iba a ir
but I had seen it here and I was
pero lo había visto aquí y estaba
[ __ ] myself, anyway, you
[__] igual
put Tomas and for dinner, let's see
a ti te pones tomás y para cenar a ver
what you want, there's an ingredient,
qué quieres que haya un ingrediente
you like this carbonara, you
a ti te gusta esta carbonara a ti te
like it more, if I pay, you put Tomas and
gusta más si pago a ti te pones tomás y
for dinner and dancing he makes
para cenar y baile
you more and for dinner and
a ti te pone hecho más y para cenar y
you go straight to dessert let's go
vais directos al postre vamos
and he shakes my hand I
y le choca la mano
get a little teary
me da un poquito de lágrimas
called literal creeps I'm telling you for
llamada grima literal os lo digo para
tears
lágrimas
what are you doing what are you
qué haces yo
doing not
qué hace
even if it was the current one it was
ni que fuera el vigente era
my mother guys who the [ __ ] does he invite those
madre mía tíos a quién [__] invita esas
things to look the other day Telmo was there
cosas mira el otro día estaba el telmo
that guy
ese tío
made a joke about a line I wanted to make
hizo un chiste de una raya quería hacer
a joke so that Kiko Rivera the
un chiste para que el kiko rivera el
Rivera guy would
chico rivera
cut him off there I uploaded the clip where
le cortó por ahí subí el clip donde
Kily uploaded it to my twitter look at them my
subió el kily a mi twitter mirarlos mi
twitter I wanted to make a joke about
twitter quería hacer un chiste de que
a line next to the food a line and
una raya al lado de la comida una raya y
I you write to you that with the
yo tú te escribe que eso con la
audience he has it was going to be unique the
audiencia que tiene iba a único la
audience he has and baines with the one
audiencia que tiene y baines con la que
I have not even with the one that anyone has it's
tengo yo ni con la que tiene nadie que
hot Telmo that one day that I've already
hace calor telmo ese un día que ya lo he
said it like eight hundred thousand times in the
dicho como ochocientas mil veces
world of vocation and it won't make sense
mundiales de vocación y no verá sentido
because I have compiled the things that he's
porque tengo recopilado las cosas que ha
been putting up and what he's been
ido poniendo y de lo que ha ido
bragging about in his history it will be far from
presumiendo en su historia distará de
how he gets the promo that he then
cómo consigue la promo que luego él
boasts about look look the brands call me
presume mira mira me llaman las marcas
the brands call me the guy  he's nobody
me llama las marcas el tío no es nadie
the guy nobody knows him the guy what he
el tío no lo conoce nadie el tío lo que
gets along with with all those
se lleva con toda esa gente de los
big people because they see him as a joke that is
grandes porque lo tienen como una gracia
not funny that he got into motorcycles
que no tiene gracia que se metió motos
in his day and that he has a hundred and something thousand
en su día y que tiene ciento y pico mil
followers because they are bots
seguidores porque son bots
and kiko rivera told him no this joke
y el kiko rivera le dijo no esta broma
how are we going to do it damn
como la vamos a hacer [__]
the ribera boy so that he has more
el chico ribera para que tenga más
sense than you you are five ribera
cabeza que tú eres cinco ribera
one day the rhythm and don't see man that is
un día la ritmo y no véase tío ese tiene
repulsive repulsive and has a very
repulsivo repulsivo y un jeta de mucho
careful face and when someone doesn't see or find
cuidado y cuando la alguien no ve ni se
out how people get the
entere la gente de cómo consigue la
promo that he flaunts the same thing they might even kick
promo de las que vacila lo mismo incluso
him out and they don't invite him
lo echa y ya no le invitan a ninguna
anywhere what he deserves to know is how he is that he
parte que lo que se merece saber es cómo
invites he has made himself so that he
está que invita se ha hecho
invites receptive to that that he is
para que invita receptiva a eso que te
going to screw you up that he is not a
va a meter la pata que no es un creador
content creator that does nothing the
de contenido que no hace nada
only thing he does on his networks
que lo único que hace en sus redes
because you get involved later and all the humor
porque tú te metes luego y todo el humor
that mirage has and drunk look I fell
que tiene mirage y borracho mira me cayó
to the floor from the drunkenness that I have for a
al suelo de la borrachera que tengo por
while the jokes are that we are
tiempo los chistes son de que estamos
drunk that he is very drunk that  I do
borrachos de que está muy bebido de que
n't know what
no sé qué
Javier I have to do so that
javier lo tengo que hacer para que
I'm not in a hurry because nobody or
tampoco me corre prisa porque nadie ni
nobody
nadie
a simple video putting it and back
un vídeo simple poniéndolo y atrás
but what he does is tremendous what he does
pero es tremendo lo que hace lo que hace
with the brands is tremendous the way he
con las marcas es tremendo la manera que
has of getting the brands is
tiene de conseguir las marcas es
tremendous when they
tremendo cuando
invite people who fall into grace
le invitan a gente que caen en gracia
for a given moment and this the greats
por un momento dado y esto los grandes
the greats have are very since
los grandes tienen son muy desde hace
this type of things of that they catch
este tipo de cosas de que cogen en
someone's grace
gracia a alguien
that they catch thanks people who do
de que cogen gracias gente
n't that are not funny it's like
que no que no tienen gracia es como
when Chose fell into grace if they have
cuando cayó en gracia el choca si lo han
made him famous for the same thing that
hecho famoso por lo mismo que tiene el
Chose has what charisma
choca que carisma
because they enter thanks because look he said
porque entran gracias porque mira dijo
about the hospital that already the whole life with
lo del hospital esa ya toda la vida con
Chose it is already well seen and we
el choque ya es bien visto y ya les
all forgive them
perdonamos todos
the one in a hurry I remember
el de la prisa yo me acuerdo
perfectly
perfectamente
but perfectly man because I remember
pero perfectamente tío porque me acuerdo
that you saw and I did not forget the one with the
que viese tú y no se me olvidó el de la
pizza before being famous the one
pizza antes de ser famoso
with the pizzas this is because Lauro
el de las pizzas este es porque el lauro
in place reacts to a video of his this is
en place reacciona un vídeo suyo este es
a man who has a restaurant
un hombre que tiene un restaurante
and that I have nothing against him nor do I
y que yo no tengo nada en contra de ni
know him nor do I know if he is a good person or not
lo conozco ni sé si es buena gente o no
good person whatever it is okay I just know that  he
es buena gente lo que sea vale solo se
really saw the feathers in his face, I
que se le vio mucho el plumero
just know that he was really seen and I
sólo sé que se le vio mucho el plumero y
'm talking about many years ago, the
esto estoy hablando de hace muchos años
guy
el tipo
to a man and commented on a video of his from the
a un hombre y comentó un vídeo de él del
3rd, the 3rd to 1, I placed a video of the
3 el del 3 a 1 emplace un vídeo del
well-known aesthetician because he made
estéticos conocido porque a uno le hizo
a video for someone,
un vídeo
okay, what happened when he
vale qué es lo que pasó que cuando a uno
made the video for someone, he never gave
le hizo el vídeo a uno nunca daba
credit to the channels he took on, they
crédito a los canales que cogía ellos
would take
cogían
laurels, he would take random characters that
lauro en cogía personaje random que a lo
maybe they didn't know and he gave it to me and yes, it's
mejor no lo conocían y dio y sí que es
true that every time I open a comment,
verdad que cada vez que abro comentaba
one
uno por lamas ganaba dos mil seguidores
by one I would gain two thousand followers, the thumbnail on Choca's but I don't know why you can see the thumbnail for Choca Plata changes while I tell you what I saw about Pino, no, maybe I was commenting on you but normally, imagine on a channel like Aurum, he
imagínate en un canal como el de aurum
mentions you and your channel gets a hundred
te menciona y tu canal se pone con cien
thousand subscribers the same day,
mil suscriptores el mismo día no
well, he, Pino, that was one who was
pues él el pino ese fue uno que
self-critical, made a humorous video
autocrítico hizo un vídeo humorístico
criticizing it, okay, well, I agree, he
criticando lo vale bien de acuerdo
put Spanair on Twitter, he
se puso a spanair le en twitter
started paying him on Twitter and these that I
se puso a pagarle en twitter y estos que
saw it  because now he answered he
lo vi porque ahora le llegó a contestar
became Spanish on twitter
se puso español en twitter
eurogas took my video and hasn't put it in
eurogas cogió mi vídeo y no ha puesto en
the channel description
la descripción del canal
and then one leaves
y entonces a uno
okay come on without problems and already
deja vale venga sin problemas y ya lo
put it and from there and they already took it
puso y a raíz de ahí y ya lo cogieron
as a joke it
como una gracia
's that these people make anyone famous like
es que esta gente hacen famoso a
that in famous to anyone and now
así en famoso a cualquiera y ahora cogió
the guy took it for the they have given fame on
el tío por la han regalado fama en
youtube
youtube
fame on youtube
fama en youtube
the joke to his restaurant because he made
la broma a su restaurante porque le hizo
a video criticism
un vídeo crítica
I don't have to give credit to the channel
yo no tengo por qué dar crédito al canal
from which I take the click
del que cojo el clic
the legitimate use is that
el uso legítimo es ese
but still place to not argue or to not
pero aún place por no discutir o por no
look bad or to put on a medal what was
queda mal o por ponerse una medalla lo
put the link
que se puso el enlace
oh the one about the pizza is not usually a
ay el de la pizza no suele ser
comment it's the other one but he laughs at the
comentario es el otro pero él se le ríe
joke he hits his hand when he
la gracia le choca la mano cuando le
makes the comment two wedges of manual
hace el comentario dos cuñas de manual
very rude because you have to hurry
muy grosero porque tienes que apurar a
the girl who is doing her job
la chica que está haciendo su trabajo
because you have to give her a hard time whether she
porque le tienes que pasar un apuro
has a partner or not if
tenga pareja o no la tenga si es que
this is independent of whether she has a
esto es independiente de que tenga
partner it is a lack of respect to her
pareja es una falta de respeto a su
partner if they know that she has a partner it is
pareja si saben que tiene pareja que me
strange to me that neither of them
extraña que ninguno de los dos
know that she is the girlfriend of  iowa it seems
sepan que es la novia de iowa
strange to me
me extraña
but it's the typical conversation in a bar between
pero es la típica conversación de un bar
two workers, one is drinking it's a
de dos obreros en un va tomando es una
third of a beer like it's not that big a
cerveza de un tercio como que no es para
handful like it's not that big a deal that she's
tanto puñado como que no es para tanto
your sister even if she's your mother let's
que sea tu hermana aunque sea tu madre a
see if it bothers her or not
ver si le incomoda o no le incomoda
neither javi feminists nor [ __ ]
ni javi feministas ni pollas
for you it's a
para usted es un comentario que incomoda
comment that bothers her it's rude let's move on to desserts which are desserts I can [ __ ] I can tell you more if she's gorgeous well gorgeous today that she's very gorgeous more me whatever anything otherwise and it's not a big deal but you're just saying like louis in der
estás diciendo en plan louis en derá
I'll put it on again that I haven't
me lo pongo otra vez que no lo haya
heard it's a comment from bricklayers
escuchado es un comentario de albañiles
look this is
mira esto
n't worth
no vale
a program and prime time
un programa y de máxima audiencia de
tweet
tuit
on a program it bothers the girl who's
en un programa incomoda a la chavala que
presenting who has been
está presentando que lleva tres días la
presenting rape very well for three days
chavala presentando violación muy bien
but she's been listening to it for three days
pero lleva tres días
and says [ __ ] man and with the
la escucha y diga [__] macho y con la
[ __ ] unnecessary things there's one
[__] que cosas innecesarias haya un
more ingredient
más
you put on tomas and for dinner I was going
a ti te pones tomás y para cenar iba
straight to dessert under the police
directo a la postre bajo el poli
this I  I hadn't seen it here I was
esto yo no lo había visto aquí yo estaba
[ __ ]
[__]
[Laughs]
[Risas]
the face alive there what the [ __ ] is
la cara viva ahí de qué [__] está
going on and the poor thing who doesn't know where to
pasando más y la pobre que no sabe dónde
hide
meterse
[Laughs] she could have
[Risas]
done it from the heart before the
lo ha podido de corazón antes que el
words first carbonara
palabras primero carbonara
I know what you want me to tell you I
yo que sé qué quieres que te diga
didn't understand the joke copyright
no entendí el chiste derecho de autor
guys I'm fed up with vane art and
tíos que estoy harto ya de vane arte y
art attic on the channel for months now
desván de arte en el canal meses ya
even the names of the people who go neo
hasta los nombres de la gente que va neo
because every now and then I get the urge to
porque de vez en cuando me me da por
bat hater so you can't comment
batear hater para que no podáis comentar
and you know what's wrong with you that I came back
y sabéis qué es lo que os pasa que volví
sack I mean I know more or less by sight or
saco o sea sé más o menos de vista o
by name by avatar the
bien por el nombre por el avatar los
haters the typical fans of the
haters los típicos fans de los canales
pathetic channels and so on and I ban you so you can't
penosos y demás y os baneo para que no
comment on the channel maybe in
podáis comentar el canal ya lo mejor a
two months like now he unbanned
los dos meses como ahora quitó el baneo
everyone and keep commenting and
a todo el mundo y seguir comentando y
like Xavi didn't even realize that you were
como ni xavi dado cuenta que estabais
banned and you're one of them we've been saying
baneado y tú eres uno de ellos llevamos
copyright for a while it's not that big of a deal it's not that big of a
un rato derecho de autor diciendo no es
deal it's not that big of a
para tanto no es para tanto no es para
deal and now you go and ask I just
tanto y ahora coges y preguntas es que
don't understand the  joke if you don't understand the
no entiendo el chiste si no entiende el
joke because you're saying it's not that big of a
chiste porque está diciendo no es para
deal because I'm being it and if I
tanto porque lo estoy siendo yo y si yo
had said that it's silly I
hubiera dicho que es una tontería te
would have told you that he's very ugly and that if he had said
hubiera dicho que es muy feo y que si
and that he had become a heartthrob there would have been
hubiera dicho y que se hubiera hecho
more applause you would have
galán hubiera más aplaudidos hubieras
said
dicho
really I am very ridiculous points the
de verdad soy muy puntos ridículos los
[ __ ] haters who came to this channel it is an
[__] haters que venía este canal es un
uncomfortable comment they are telling her
comentario incómodo le están diciendo
that she is very good that they would take her to
que está muy buena que se la llevaban al
dessert what does the joke
postre que significa el chiste
mean what does the joke mean
qué significa el chiste
a sketch is needed for all of these
hace falta un croquis para todos estos
how is copyright or
como es el derecho de autor o
obviously
evidentemente sí
a sketch is needed so as not to understand
hace falta un croquis para no entender
the joke that she is very good that they would have
el chiste que está muy buena que se
dessert with her they would go to
tomarían con ella el postre se irían a
have dessert what is he
tomarse el postre que es lo que les está
telling them that he would take her where
diciendo que se la llevaría donde hace
a sketch is needed
falta un croquis
even to a drawing on a blackboard
aun a un dibujito por una pizarrita
what is dessert this is [ __ ] up these
qué es el postre está toma por culo
are situations that are experienced many
son situaciones que se viven muchas
times no and surely in your family you would have
veces no y seguro que en vuestra familia
heard like and in your
habría escuchado como y en vuestro
circle comments like that and you there well
círculo comentarios así y tal y tú ahí
[ __ ] can continue listening to me but of
pues [__] puede seguir escucharme pero
course more if a poor woman doesn't know where to
claro más si una pobre no sabe dónde
go there no and many times
meterse ahí no y muchas veces la vida
real life knows how to answer fact you fall
real sabe cómo contesta hecho te caes
short me  It's going to happen to me, it's happened to me
corta me va a pasar a mí me ha pasado
that maybe they made a
que a lo mejor me han hecho hace un
mediocre comment about Lorena and I'm like, what do I do?
regulín sobre lorena y me quedo así que
I go blank, I don't even
digo que hago me pongo en blanca ni me
get into the subject, it's a
pongo en paso del tema está que es un
compliment, I take it as a compliment but
halago me lo tomo como un halago pero
everything knows how to tremble
todo como sabe temblar
you can pay a compliment to a woman
tú le puedes echar un piropo a una mujer
of course, just pay a compliment, have a
claro solo pues hecha un piropo tenga
partner and have a partner, tours you can pay it
pareja y tenga pareja tours lo puedes
but what you like is not
pero a ti lo que te gusta no es la
mozzarella it's more like this
mozzarella es más así
and what you like is more and more and this you
y lo que te gusta es más y más y esto tú
take it to the dessert directly
te la llevas al postre directamente
man my god two gentlemen of 50 or 60
hombre por dios dos señores de 50 o 60
years old I don't know how old those two are, he does
años no sé cuánto tendrá esos dos
n't want to break the roll either it's not that it
no quiere cortar el rollo tampoco es que
's complicated of course because more if he doesn't want to
es complicado claro porque más si no
stop there I decided to listen to myself
quiere pararse ahí decidí escucharme
not
no
in agreement with here not because she doesn't want to
de acuerdo con aquí no porque no quiere
create
generar
the uncomfortable situation for herself
ella la situación incómoda para ella
but she doesn't want the situation to be
pero no quiere que la situación se
uncomfortable for him in general you know that it's
incómoda para él en general saber que es
typical of
lo típico de
[Music]
[Música]
that it shouldn't be like that's how I eat
que no debería ser así es como yo me
the comment but I'm not returning it to you
como el comentario pero a ti no te lo
because then the discomfort
devuelvo porque entonces la incomodidad
is greater  because if it is that I do not know well
es mayor porque si es que no sé bueno
what do you want me to tell you
qué quieres que te diga
things
cosas que
that are unnecessary and that's it
cosas que son innecesarias y ya está
but well what I already told you I do
pero bueno que ya te digo a esta gente
not dislike these people I do not dislike Pino
no me cae mal a mí pino no me cae mal
at all and Cesar is a little the times
para nada y césar está un poco las veces
that we have been with them especially the
que hemos estado con ellos sobre todo el
other day that we had yesterday in private with
otro día que tuvimos ayer en privado con
it and such they are super they are very good
ello y tal son súper son muy buenas
people they are very kind people they are
gentes son gente muy amables son gente
very attentive people but they have their things let me be that they
muy atenta pero tienen sus cosas sea yo
have their things and that's it
que se tienen sus cosas y ya está
Will Smith
will smith
[Music]
[Música]
yes yes I Walt out of myself can you
sí sí yo walt fuera de mí me podéis
make a meme Paulo please for twitter
hacer un meme paulo por fa para twitter
a meme that comes out
un meme que salga
and Giovanna in the head their head
y giovanna en la cabeza la cabeza de
goes for that a lot of head no auan sorry sorry
ellos van por eso mucha cabeza no auan
their head goes in
la cabeza de ellos van en el cuerpo de
Will Smith's body and Pino's head
will smith y la cabeza de pino
in Rock S's body well the head
en el cuerpo de rock s bueno la cabeza
is a tree
es es árbol
at least please
al menos porfa
but I as for the level of contest I did
pero yo en cuanto a nivel de concurso yo
not I noticed in him in the final I noticed like they
no yo noté en él en la final note como
had us in line or the android
que nos tenían en fila o al androide a
I do not know why I
mí no sé por qué
noticed that we were carrying a plate and of a great
notaba que llevábamos un plato y de gran
plan of this  people what the [ __ ] are you bringing
plan de esta gente que [__] trae
don't get upset my admired king of
no te alteres mi admirado rey del
salsa you are unique you dominate immaculate it
salsero eres único tu domina inmaculada
was like she was already
era como que ya era la
preparing for some [ __ ]
prepararse para una [__]
Paula but pine not from pine no Paula from 6
paula pero pino no de pino no paula de 6
trees who is the one who said no and
árboles que es el que le ha dicho no y
we weren't carrying [ __ ] at least I consider this mind I say I have no idea about cooking but I say it because I also tried many things that we did in I provide it to say let's see if we haven't passed in something
decir a ver si no hemos pasado en algo
like that let's see if this is but I didn't know
tal a ver si está esto pero no sabía
[ __ ] at all the salmorejo was very
[__] para nada el salmorejo estaba muy
good the tartar was very good too
bueno el tartar estaba muy bueno también
I had to have the tartar and dance one more day and from the
yo el tartar debía y baile día más y de
dial the boss gave it to Felipe and
dial el capo le di a felipe y todo el
everyone said it is very good both you
mundo dijo está muy bueno tanto usted
well
bueno
says Oliver my goodness there will only be to
dice oliver madre mía sólo habrá de
crash Oliver
chocar oliver
the level the level dear we are
el nivel el nivel queridos estamos
talking about Iowa
hablando de iowa
Oliver are you okay Javi
oliver estás bien
Javi back taken by Choca Oliver
javi javi atrás tomado por choca oliver
back taken does not exist
atrás tomado no existe
Oliver we can help you with something Oliver
oliver te podemos ayudar en algo oliver
Oliver is already lost on the internet or like
oliver ya está perdió en internet o como
Oliver who is past
oliver que está pasado
cured thank you very much king hey family
curó muchas gracias rey oye familia
remember that prime is free yes
recordaros que los prime son gratis si
you have both are prime or live we can
tenéis ambas son prime o live te podemos
help you dear are for having that opinion
ayudar querido son por tener esa opinión
before taking it and when I take it and
antes de llevarlo y cuando lo lleve y
we finish fifth Oliver in the show
quedamos quinto oliver en el show
Oliver is the chocas
oliver es el chocas
2 after sorry I just finished
2 después de perdón se me acabó de
accessing and loading it's that I don't know or rather they had
acceder y carge es que no sé o sea
eaten prima jean he has the
se habían comiendo a prima jean tiene la
box on the plate and it was like take the
caja en el plato y era como toma la
tip or whatever it is so bad he is
punta o sea lo que sea tan malo está
and
e
maybe a little [ __ ] but being
a lo mejor un poco subnormal pero siendo
from the kitchen he doesn't talk about literally the
de cocina no habla de literalmente el
dessert maybe yes but don't be the Caesar of
postre igual sí pero no sea el césar de
the videos
los vídeos
watch out that for five years he has said to talk
ojo que ya cinco años ha dicho
literally about the post but
que hable literalmente del poste pero
there is a circuit you don't have to be very
hay que circuito no hay que ser muy
stupid to think that people and I I I have
tonto para pensar eso gente y yo yo yo
not done any moment that is to be
no he hecho ningún momento que es estar
calling people for nothing everyone we have
llama a la gente para nada todo el mundo
comments and we have attitudes
tenemos comentarios y tenemos actitudes
that well that no that no that they do not come from everyone all all all all all some more some
que bueno que no que no que no proceden
less no it depends on
todos unos más otros menos no depende
the context too but I have said
del contexto también pero yo he dicho
that people are called for nothing it does not
que se llama la gente para nada a mí no
seem like it to me either I do not know it has been
me lo parece tampoco lo conozco se ha
seen once in my life but they did not
visto una vez mi vida pero no se
meet logically that
encontraron lógicamente esa
you are sending me Paulo something else
usted me está mandando paulo otra cosa
leave me a second that you will know that  I
dejarme un segundo que lo sabrá que lo
have it at home because he's sending me
tengo en casa porque me está mandando
something else unpleasant
otra cosa desagradable
for nothing
para nada
but it's almost at the same time it's
pero es casi en el mismo momento
almost at the same time also let's see
es casi en el mismo momento además a ver
well it's not the same it's not the same day
bueno no es el mismo no es el mismo día
no
no
because I think more if it was like with
porque creo que más si estaba como con
other clothes I don't think it's
otras ropa no
not the same day have you will
creo que no es el mismo día
see if the same and them two
habéis vais a ver si igual y ellos dos
too but more if not it's not the same
también pero más si no no es el mismo
day no what we
día no
say other
lo que decimos otros
communicating products of realization that you eat period what's
comunicantes de realización que comes
happening with the pineapple
que pasa con la piña
incoming call from a private number
llamada entrante de un número privado
and what's the problem come on fine
y qué problema tiene venga fino
a pizza
una pizza
because the truth is a
porque la verdad
silly comment that can get you scared a little
comentario baboso que te puede llevar a
bit
un sustito
to a little bit what do you mean
a un sustito que es a qué te refieres
by the subscribed
con el suscrito
family look at my twitter
familiar mira en mi twitter
look at my twitter I
mira en mi twitter
had seen their video
había visto el vídeo de
especially if you crash I don't know who is
ellos sobre todo si chocas no sé quién
beautiful but I made the video of you touch it
es bello pero yo el vídeo de tocas lo
like a year ago he
hice como hace un año
said something new
ha dicho algo nuevo
look how very clear that if it's true that we ca
mira que bien claro que si de verdad es
n't
que no podemos
no no no no why do they call them mobility
no no no no porque les llaman movilidad
well be like he vomits with the
bueno sea como que vomita con la
community well I don't know what it's been it
comunidad bueno no sé que sido tampoco
's not a joke no it's not that much that no I don't
es una broma no tampoco es para tanto
know grown up  I would refer to the dessert if I
no sé crecido se referiría el postre si
hadn't made the comment before that
antes no hubiese hecho el comentario de
you like it more and of course another
a ti te gusta más y claro a que otra
person takes it wrong and hits their face
persona lo toma mal y le parte la cara
another person takes it wrong and hits their
que otra persona lo toma mal y le parte
face let's
la cara
see let's see it
a ver a ver
wouldn't be very normal either to hit
no sería muy normal tampoco partir de la
someone's face that's why it's like me in
cara a alguien por eso sea en plan yo en
that type of things to have to change the
ese tipo de cosas para tener cambiar la
screen's location in that type of things
pantalla de sitio en ese tipo de cosas
I
yo
are true in how it is precisely like
son ciertas en cómo es precisamente como
the desktop Juanes is so perfect
la de escritorio juanes es tan perfecto
they are things that you don't know how to react
son cosas que no sabes cómo reaccionar
at the moment
en el momento
why
por qué
the uncomfortable ones and you can create the
las incómodas y puedes crear la
situation even more uncomfortable then you are there
situación todavía más incómoda entonces
a bit against the wall until
estás hay un poco ante la pared hasta
then for me the one that is
entonces para mí el que el que es
regrettable on the part of the person who
lamentable por parte de la persona que
calls it this famous one of the
lo llama este famoso del
first comment was for
primer comentario era para muchas
thank you very much referring to the pool more
gracias referirse al pool más
directly to the dessert is intro I say
directamente al postre es intro digo
clearly literally [ __ ] already goes
claro literalmente [__]
to dessert it is to go to [ __ ]
ya pasa al postre es pasar a [__]
exactly speaking clearly in case maybe you do
exacto hablando claro por si a lo mejor
n't understand you don't read between the lines what garlic
no entiende no lees entre líneas que ajo
but well as they have seen each other
pero bueno como ellos sí se han visto
more times I also don't know what level of
más veces yo tampoco sé qué nivel de
fun these people have because
cachondeo tiene esta gente porque
Maximino Omar and Face Stars have seen each other
maximino omar y face stars se han visto
in all these programs they have spoken a
en todo estos programas han hablado
lot in private they have been there
mucho en privado han estado ahí
preparing programs  they have been there for a long
preparando programas han anterior mucho
time much longer than many people
tiempo mucho más tiempo que mucha gente
in plan together to talk I don't know
en plan juntos de hablar yo no sé hasta
how far trust goes but of course
qué nivel llega la confianza pero claro
the problem is that it is there
el problema es eso que está ahí en
live but well seeing the face of
directo pero bueno viendo la cara de
masses and no no no literally no literally not
masas y no no no literalmente no
having a second put
literalmente no haber un segundo ponga
a meme let's
un meme
see a little tacky no paulo stop from him
a ver un poco cutre no paulo para de él
a kiss
un beso
paulo but with what has he cut this let's
paulo pero con que ha recortado esto a
see the meme the meme of course I care about
ver el meme el meme claro el me importa
the meaning like the quality
el significado en plan la calidad
is not that important
tampoco es tan importante
but with what the [ __ ] cut in your paulo
pero con qué [__] recortado en tu paulo
ah
ah
waterfall paulo of points seeing the face
cascada paulo de puntos viendo la cara
that puts on at
que pone la a
no level of trust that even
ningún nivel de confianza que incluso
if a colleague tells her
aunque se lo diga un colega
next to a colleague a friend does not make
junto a una colega una amiga no le hace
a joke that you are going to [ __ ] ball that
una broma de que te vas a [__] bola
happens of rapier
que pasa de estoque
in nowhere it
en la nada
is a pain I do not know how to [ __ ] teach me it
es una putada no sé [__] me enseñas yo
is not a pain either why do
es una putada por qué
many people give a damn about
a mucha gente le da palo el
countering those types of comments
contrarrestar ese tipo de comentarios
seriously bad vibes and being blunt it
con seriedad mal rollo y siendo tajante
should not be like that but many times
no debería ser así pero muchas veces
this happens many times it happens for not
pasa esto muchas veces pasa por no
reaching a more uncomfortable situation
llegar a una situación más incómoda
still a person has to swallow
todavía una persona tiene que tragarse
the comment
el comentario
and this happens no matter how much you tell me that
y esto pasa por mucho que me digáis que
no this happens they
no esto pasa
make a comment
te sueltan un comentario
you take it here in your chest and the
tú te lo lleva aquí en el pecho y el
rest don't say anything so
resto no dice nada por
as not to take it to another level in fact we
por no llevarlo a otra escala de hecho
cut off every moment what the [ __ ] did you say she
cortamos todo momento qué [__] has dicho
knows when the other one says it thinking it
sabe cuando lo otro lo dice creyéndose
's a joke and this
que es una broma sin más y esto pasa
always happens and it's a [ __ ] and you know I feel really
siempre y es una putada y me sabes súper
bad for her of course I mean it doesn't
mal por ella claro o sea no
come out super bad but well
me sale súper mal pero bueno que a ella
I ask her more and she'll probably tell me
yo le pregunto a más y seguro me dice
that I don't give a damn I know her and I know that if at
que me la suda la conozco y sé que si en
the moment man I know that you're not going to
el momento hombre me desde que no te va
lose sleep over what that guy says
a quitar el sueño lo que diga ese tío
but come on it's pathetic
pero vamos lamentable
but oh well
pero bueno
when the show ended she gave her a
cuando terminó el programa le dio un
tarlay hug a pinoles hug and
abrazo de tarlay un abrazo pinoles y
everyone said goodbye and she had a
todo el mundo se despidió y ella se la
super good time and she's super
pasaron súper bien y está súper
grateful that she was going to and Carmen
agradecida de que iba a y carmen le
gave her that opportunity and I
hayan dado esa oportunidad y yo también
am also of course super grateful
por supuestísimo estoy súper agradecido
that you trust in her for whatever it is that on
de que confiéis en ella para lo que sea
top of that she is invited upstairs
es que encima de eso se la invita arriba
and given the opportunity she is there
y le da la oportunidad está ahí
what are you going to do she
qué vas a hacer
is going to create a bad vibe on the show it
va a crear un mal rollo en el programa
is that the girls had to eat
es que se ha tenido que comer las
the one who has it  had to eat the
el que se la ha tenido que comer la
girl
chavala
what anger more audio more agora is what
qué coraje más de audio más ágora es lo
makes me angry buddy
que me da coraje amiguito
words to me because you know that there is one
palabras a mí porque sabéis que hay one
also I think it is ink with a turnip
también la creo que es tinta con una
leg man
pata del nabo tío
but it is not going to create a bad vibe
pero tampoco va a crear un mal rollo
now you know
ahora sabe
and it is going to turn white or clear
y se va a poner blanca ni claro
obviously
evidentemente
but it makes me angry it
pero me da coraje
makes me a lot thanks to situations jon
me da mucho gracias a situaciones jon de
really I
verdad yo
see it from afar with a pride that you
lo veo desde lejos con un orgullo que ya
know when I had to watch all the
sabes yo cuando tenía que ver todos los
disaster chefs programs because the
programas de disaster chefs porque yo el
first but the second the third and the
primero pero el segundo el tercero y el
fourth because I saw them here with you and I
cuarto por los vi aquí con vosotros y yo
cut directly and I did not see why she was
cortaba directo y no veía porque estaba
if she was not there I would not have
a ella si no estuviese allá no había
cut my thing was cut solely and
cortado yo mi cosa se cortaba única y
exclusively because she was
exclusivamente porque estaba ella
presenting and I wanted to see it and it makes me
presentando y quería verlo y me hace
very excited and I see it as, I mean it's
mucha ilusión y lo veo como o sea es
like someone I know from their
como si alguien yo que sé de sus
families doing something and it makes you excited
familias haciendo algo y te hace ilusión
and you want to see how we do it and I am
y quieres ver cómo lo hacemos y yo me
very happy that they have trusted
alegro un montón de que hayan confiado
her because I consider that she has done
en ella porque yo considero que se le ha
very, very, very well man and
dado muy muy muy muy bien tío y la da
all of Uruguay and
todo el uruguay y
variety gives it courage, honestly it makes me angry
variedad coracia sinceramente da coraje
because it is that I do not know  a little thin skin
porque es que no sé un poco piel fina
too what he's doing
también lo que está haciendo
is a little [ __ ] for a little while I know
es un poco una [__] un ratito se una
what's
lo que se
being said on
está diciendo en
the show
el programa
too but it was cool man it was
también pero que estuvo guapo tío estuvo
water for the truth I was having a
agua por la verdad yo me lo pasaba muy
great time and I but lamentable and shameful
bien y me pero lamentable y vergonzoso
the opposition so so low or imaginary
la oposición tan tan baja o imaginario
that your father does it to a chat about
que lo hace vuestro padre a una charla
affairs there couple and a moment ago
de lances ahí pareja y hace un momento
Diego good reluctant to Fabio is
el diego buen reacia a fabio está
crazy the
colgado de la [__] cabeza el diego de
real Diego Diego kept making fun of
verdad el diego no paraba de mandando
Andrei to me my kids good
guasa al andrei a mí mis niños mucha
luck here rich good luck my
suerte aquí rico a mucha suerte mis
kids you're going to be doubling it
niños lo vais a ser doblándolo
don't see I had only won against the guy with the
no vea sólo había ganado al tío de la
mask of dismissed more what I don't know what it's
máscara de cesado más lo que no sé cómo
called
se llama
well lamentable lamentable family I
bueno lamentable lamentable familia no
can't it's something else it has made me feel bad to
puedo es otra cosa me ha sentado mal a
my uncle I don't know them I
mi tío no los conozco
just got home from work what
acabo de llegar de trabajar que ha
happened from the mind quick summary
pasado de la mente resumen rápido
quick summary you
resumen rápido
see now that he already had this deal
lo ves ahora que ya tuvo este trato
[Music]
[Música]
ah
ah